In feedforward neural networks,
在前馈神经网络中
the output at any time is a function of the current input and the weights alone.
任何时刻的输出都是当前输入和权重的函数
We assume that the inputs are independent of each other.
我们假设输入是相互独立的
Therefore, there is no significance to the sequence.
所以这对序列没有意义
So we actually train the system by randomly drawing inputs and target pairs.
我们实际上通过随机选取输入和目标对训练系统
In RNNs, our output at time t,
在循环神经网络中 我们在时间 t 的输出
depends not only on the current input and weights,
不仅取决于当前输入和权重
but also on previous inputs.
还依赖于之前的输入
Such as the input to time T minus 1,
如输入 T-1
T minus 2 and so on.
t-2 等等
So, how can we visualize that?
那么我们如何进行可视化呢？
Let's look at our neural network again.
我们再次观察这个神经网络
We have an input x and output y and a hidden layer s. Remember s?
我们有输入 x 输出 y 和一个隐藏层 s 还记得 s 吗？
It stands for State,
它代表状态
which is a term we use when the system has memory.
系统包含存储时 我们使用这个术语
Wx represents the weight matrix,
Wx 代表
connecting the inputs to the state layer.
连接输入和状态的权重矩阵
Wy represents the weight matrix,
Wy 代表
connecting the state to the output and Ws represents the weight matrix,
连接状态和输出的权重矩阵 Ws 代表
connecting the state from the previous timestep to the state in the next timestep.
连接之前时间步长和接下来时间步长状态的权重矩阵
Notice that the single s is fed back to the system.
注意只有一个 s 反馈到系统
In every single timestep,
在每个单独的时间步长中
the system will look the same.
系统看起来是相同的
This is what we call the folded model.
我们把它叫做折叠模型
Since the input is spread over time and we
由于输入随着时间是分散的
performed the same task for every element in the sequence,
我们在输入语句中为每个要素执行相同任务
we can unfold the model in time and represent it the following way.
我们可以恰当展开模型 把它表示成下列方式
Just as an example,
正如例子所示
you can see that the output at time T plus 2,
你会看到时间 T+2 的输出
depends on the input at time T plus 2 on the way
取决于时间 t+2 的输入
matrices and also on all previous inputs.
以及所有之前的输入
Let's use the following definitions,
我们使用以下定义
x of t is the input vector at time t,
Xt 是时间 t 的输入向量
y of t is the output vector at time t and s of t is
Yt 是时间 t 的输出向量 St 是
the hidden state vector at time t. In feedforward neural networks,
是时间 t 的状态向量 在前馈神经网络中
we use an activation function to obtain the hidden layer h. And all we
我们使用激活函数得到隐藏层 h
need are the inputs and the weight matrix connecting the inputs to the hidden layer.
我们只需要输入 以及连接输入和隐藏层的权重
In RNNs, we use an activation function to obtain s,
在循环神经网络中 我们使用激活函数得到 s
but with a slight twist.
不过存在些微差别
The input to the activation function is now the sum of one,
现在输入到激活函数是一个总和
the product of the inputs and their corresponding weight matrix,
即输入及其对应权重矩阵 Wx 的乘积
Wx and two, the product of
加上
the previous activation values and their corresponding weight matrix Ws.
之前激活值及其对应权重矩阵 Ws 的乘积
The output vector is calculated exactly the same as in feedforward neural networks.
输出向量的计算方法与前馈神经网络中完全相同
It can be a linear combination of the inputs to
它等于通向对应权重矩阵 Wy 的每个输出节点
each output node with a corresponding weight matrix
输入的线性组合
Wy or for example a soft max function of the same linear combination.
例如相同线性组合的 Softmax 函数
Notice, that RNNs share the same parameters during each timestep.
注意在每个时间步长中 循环神经网络的参数相同
So although intuitively, it appears that RNNs are more
所以虽然从直观上来看 循环神经网络看似
complicated than feedforward neural networks since they have memory.
比前馈神经网络更加复杂 因为他们包含存储
In practice, the number of parameters that need to be learned remains modest.
实际上需要学习的参数数量并不多
The unfolding scheme we mentioned is generic and can be
我们提到的展开模型是通用的
adjusted according to the neural network architecture we aim to build.
可以根据我们创建神经网络结构的目标进行调整
We can decide how many inputs and outputs we need.
我们可以决定所需要的输入和输出数量
For example in sentiment analysis,
例如在情感分析中
we can have many inputs and a single output that spans the spectrum of happy to sad.
我们有多个输入和一个输出 表达从高兴到伤心的图谱
Another example can be time series predictions,
另一个例子就是时间序列预测
where we may have many inputs and many outputs which are not necessarily aligned.
其中包括许多不对齐的输入和输出
RNNs can be stacked like Legos,
循环神经网络可以和乐高一样堆叠
just as feedforward neural networks can.
与前馈神经网络类似
For example, we can have the output of a single RNN level, say,
比如说 我们拥有单个循环神经网络的输出
vector y become the input to a second layer whose output is vector o.
如向量 y 成为第二层的输入 而第二层的输出是向量 o
Each layer operates independently of the other layers,
每一层都和另一层独立运算
as architecturally it doesn't matter where the inputs
如同建筑一样 输入和
come from or where the outputs are headed to.
输出的方向并不会产生影响